Guide to the John Latimer papers, 1890-1990 MS0370.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Personal papers, 1944-1988; MS0370 Series 1; 9.0 Linear feet (Box 19, Box 13)
  - Glass Slides: Taormina excavation, undated (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Glass Slides: Taormina, undated (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown--city architecture, undated (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Glass Slides: Avernus--lake scene, undated (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown--coastal scene, undated (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Glass Slides: Solfothra, undated (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Glass Slides: Partial map of Italy, undated (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Glass Slides: Old map of Napoli and surrounding area, undated (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown map of ancient city, undated (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Glass Slides: Tower of Tergil--Naples, undated (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Glass Slides: Funicular to Vesuvius, undated (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Glass Slides: Vesuvius lava field, undated (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown--small city scene, undated (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Glass Slides: Forum--Pompei, undated (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Glass Slides: Pompei house, undated (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Glass Slides: Capua, undated (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Glass Slides: Amphitheater--Capua, undated (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Glass Slides: Tomb of Vergil (?)--Naples, undated (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Glass Slides: Capo Miseno, undated (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown--excavation, undated (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Glass Slides: Cumal, undated (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown--inside a building, undated (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Glass Slides: Via Domitiana, undated (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Glass Slides: Arco Felice, undated (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Glass Slides: Villa Cumae, undated (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Glass Slides: Cumae, undated (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Glass Slides: Grotto of Sybil, undated (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Glass Slides: Amalfi, undated (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Glass Slides: South of Amalfi, undated (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Glass Slides: Temple of Concord (?), undated (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Glass Slides: Lake Lucrinus, undated (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Glass Slides: Grotto of Sybil, undated (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Glass Slides: Map of Akragas, undated (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown temple, undated (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown temple, undated (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Glass Slides: Lake Akernus, undated (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown--door, undated (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown--tunnel, undated (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown--ocean scene, undated (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Glass Slides: Bridge of Sighs, undated (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Glass Slides: San Marino, undated (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Glass Slides: Tusculum, undated (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Glass Slides: Lake Albanos, undated (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Glass Slides: Sabine Farm, undated (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Glass Slides: Waterfall-fons Bandusia, undated (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - Glass Slides: Rubicon, undated (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - Glass Slides: Lavinium, undated (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - Glass Slides: Lavinium--Practica, undated (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - Glass Slides: Unknown ruins, undated (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - Glass Slides: Rimini, undated (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - Glass Slides: Lake Albanus, undated (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Glass Slides: Ravello, undated (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Glass Slides: Mons Albanus, undated (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - Glass Slides: Venice--St. Marks Square, undated (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Glass Slides: Como, undated (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Glass Slides: Fiesoli, undated (Box 19, Folder 127)
- Personal papers, 1940-1987; MS0370 Series 2; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 20)
  This series consists of speeches, biographical info, syllabi, articles, and the American Classical League newsletter. The material dates from 1940-87.
  - American Classical League Newsletter Fall, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 08/1965 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 02/1966-09/1966 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 01/1967-09/1967 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 09/1968 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 01/1969-09/1969 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 01/1970-09/1970 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 01/1971-09/1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 01/1972-09/1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 01/1973-09/1973 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 01/1974-09/1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 01/1975-09/1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - American Classical League Newsletter, 01/1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report of Faculty Members, 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Lectures, etc., 1970-1985 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Correspondences, Memo, 1964-1987 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Course Syllabus and Bibliographies, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - C.V. and Biographical Information of Latimer, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - The Life of George Washington in Latin Prose - Correspondence, Etc., undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Nominees for GW Honorary Degrees, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Speeches/Papers The Pony Express, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Speeches/Papers- Robert Middlekauff. Ancients and Axioms: Secondary Education in the Eighteenth Century -New England, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Speeches/Papers - Seven Wise Men of Colonial America, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Speeches/Papers- Executive Secretary's Annual Report, 06/19/1969 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Speeches/Papers - ACL- One Man's View, 06/1969 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Speeches/Papers - Classical Traditions in early America, 10/09/1970-10/10/1979 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Speeches/Papers - Excerpts from talk, 10/30/1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Speeches/Papers - Resolution: In memory of Honorary Trustee Sidney William Souers, 01/17/1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Speeches/Papers - Diogenes Laertius - Lives of Eminent Philosophers, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Speeches/Papers- Priority Needs for Classics, 1968-1975 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Speeches/Papers - The Classical Humanities in a Changing World, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Speeches/Papers - We See by The Papers, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Speeches/Papers - Education in a Democracy, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Speeches/Papers - America's second battle of the books, undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Speeches/Papers - No Withered Leaves, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Speeches/Papers - Latin in the Secondary Schools: A Six Year Program, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Speeches/Papers - Language Literature and the Liberal Arts, undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Speeches/Papers - Cultural and Social Values in a Materialistic Society, undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Speeches/Papers - Classical Studies in American Education, undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Speeches/Papers - And Gladly Learn, undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Speeches/Papers - The Tower of Babel, undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Speeches/Papers - Testimony on S.S16, undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Speeches/Papers -, 05/1940-11/1951 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Published Articles, 1960-1967 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Published Articles, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Published Articles, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Published Articles, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Published Articles, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 48)